Office of Finance and Planning Records UA048
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Finance and Planning Records
1977 -- 1993
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Finance Division
Administration and Finance Committee
UA048
1.25 Linear Feet 3 boxes
This collection contains the records of the Office of Finance and Planning.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Financing/Capital planning; Committee records; and Planning and budgeting.
Custodial History
Transfer of University Records to the archives from the Office of Finance and Planning, circa 1989.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of the Office of Finance and Planning, including agendas, memoranda, minutes, committee reports, and budgets.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Finance; Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Facilities
- Financing/Capital Planning, 1984 -- 1993; UA048.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records on Capital Projects and Financing from the Office of Finance and Planning
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged first alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Capital Projects, 1985 -- 1990; UA048.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Capital Projects FY, 1989 -- 1993; UA048.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Major Risks, Contingency Analyses, 1985 -- 1987; UA048.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - University Capital Plan/Financing, 1984; UA048.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
- Committee Records, 1977 -- 1986; UA048.002; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains Committee Records from the Office of Finance and Planning.
  - Academic Council: Supplementary Materials, 1977 -- 1979; UA048.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Academic Council: Minutes and Agendas, 1979 -- 1980; UA048.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Academic Council: Minutes and Agendas, 1980 -- 1981; UA048.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Minutes and Agendas, 1980 -- 1981; UA048.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Agendas, 1981 -- 1982; UA048.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Retreat, 1982; UA048.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Materials, 1982 -- 1983; UA048.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Retreat, 1983; UA048.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Role and Purpose, 1983 -- 1984; UA048.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Libraries, 1984 -- 1985; UA048.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Staff Council: Materials, 1986; UA048.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - University Council: Minutes and Agendas, 1980 -- 1981; UA048.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - University Council: Minutes, 1981 -- 1982; UA048.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - University Council: Minutes and Materials, 1982 -- 1983; UA048.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - University Council: Minutes, Agendas, and Materials, 1983 -- 1984; UA048.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - University Council: Minutes, Agendas, and Materials, 1984 -- 1985; UA048.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
- Planning and Budgeting, 1981 -- 1988; UA048.003; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains records on Budgeting and Planning techniques and university planning process from the Office of Finance and Planning.
  - Budgeting Techniques/Planning Process, 1981 -- 1988; UA048.003.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Planning and Budgeting, 1981 -- 1984; UA048.003.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Planning Process/Program Plan Summary, 1982 -- 1985; UA048.003.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Vet School Massachusetts Contract, 1983 -- 1984; UA048.003.001.00004 (Box 1)